let's see, he posted a video of grefg here
a ver ha puesto aquí un vídeo de grefg
I demand that you apologize
te exijo que pidas disculpas de
immediately very good my people Welcome
inmediato muy buenas mi gente Bienvenido
to the dump the awards are exploding
al vertedero los premios es la explotan
everywhere I sincerely wanted to
por todo sitio yo sinceramente Quería
give a message of calm to the
dar un mensaje de tranquilidad para el
rest of the streamers because I see that
resto de streamers porque veo que está
the subject is very hot do not argue Enough is
el tema es muy caliente no discutáis Ya
enough the award for streamer of the year I am
basta el premio al streamer del año lo
going to win it I am the best really do not
voy a ganar yo soy el mejor de verdad no
enjoy it if It is evident that I am going to
disfrutáis si Es evidente que lo voy a
win it let's see this thing about auron and I have
ganar yo a ver esto de auron y lo he
seen it more or less superficially I understand
visto más o menos por encima entiendo
that they are doing it to
que lo están haciendo para darle
publicize the event and give it play you
publicidad al evento y darle juego lo
are doing it to publicize it and
estás haciendo para darle publicidad y
stir up the hornets' nest a little there of the
mover un poco el avispero ahí de del
game okay so that they get stung
juego vale para que se piquen ahí los
there the kids go vote for some sacks to the other sack okay all that is missing would be a robbery of balls we want to discuss about second we can debate me the second position I have doubt now the award I am really going to win it Do not seriously scratch that there is a
verdad No rayéis en serio que hay una
ray It is obvious I mean if you list
rayada Es evidente O sea si te enumera
the things that I have done this year it is that I do
las cosas que he hecho este año es que
not fit I mean I have to have a
no me caben o sea tengo que tener un
[ __ ] event notebook  of the entire
[__] cuaderno de eventos de todo el
prize, we'll see, starting
premio ya veremos a ver empezando
Gregorio, it seems to me a complete
Gregorio me parece una completa
shame that you said this, this year
vergüenza que dijeras esto en este año
the community is going to decide more than ever
la comunidad va a decidir más que nunca
and the community is you and that now,
y la comunidad sois vosotros y que ahora
today, after everything that has
a día de hoy después de todo lo que ha
happened and we have seen, you have the nerve to
pasado y hemos visto tengas la cara de
maintain it
mantenerlo
because in the end it is still an event
porque al final no deja de ser un evento
that is going to be done on my camera on
que se va a hacer en mi cámara el 29 de
January 29th live and that it is going to be done at
enero en directo y que se va a hacer en
the National Auditorium in Mexico on
el auditorio nacional de México el 29 de
January 29th and that all the tickets have already sold.
enero y que ha venido ya todas las
So he has done it,
entradas O sea que ha hecho soldado
guys, and we are talking about 10,000
chavales y estamos hablando de 10.000
tickets, we are talking about something very
entradas estamos hablando de algo muy
serious, something that is no longer a project of
serio algo que ya no es un proyecto de
Greg's. Last year it could be understood
Greg el año pasado se podía entender
as a project of mine, as a project of
como un proyecto mío como un proyecto de
Greg's, but this year, not this year, I think
Greg pero este año no este año yo creo
that the great leap and the great
que ya el gran salto y la gran
difference
diferencia
in the Spanish-speaking community to see
de la comunidad hispanohablante a ver
something that says that people are
una cosa que diga que la gente lo está
considering it a project of the community
considerando un proyecto de la comunidad
because it is true that the majority
porque sí que es verdad que la mayoría
of the internet is considering it as if it
de internet lo está considerando como si
were something official, but another thing is that
fuera algo oficial pero otra cosa es que
you maintain it. No, no, family, this
tú lo mantengas no no familia que esto
is not official, I do what I  it comes out
no es oficial que yo hago lo que me sale
of the dick that the event is mine I
de la [__] que el evento es mío me
am explaining myself or I am not
estoy explicando o no me estoy
explaining myself So you make
explicando O sea que tú dejes claro la
things clear but don't sell it as something you
cosa pero que no lo vendas como algo
know in an original way it is not a reward
sabe en plan original no la recompensa
an awards gala to award to
una gala de premios para galardonar para
recognize the merit of all the content
reconocer el mérito de todo el contenido
created live which is what day after
creado en directo que es el que día tras
day unites us here on Twitch and
día pues nos une aquí en Twitch y
mainly on Twitch but also there
principalmente en Twitch pero también
are many people who do it on
pues hay mucha gente que lo hace en
YouTube and all that category if you did not
YouTube y todo eso categoría si no se
dare to your Norman makes
animó a tus Norman hace contenido en
live content you chose Javi by hand and
directo a Javi lo sacaste a dedo y
because you felt like it with respect
porque te dio la gana con respeto
more points than him by far you
más puntos que él con diferencia te cae
dislike him did that happen in some other category it makes me laugh
mal pasó eso en alguna otra categoría me
a lot
hace mucha gracia
is that if this year I had decided
es que si este año yo hubiera decidido
something I could tell you well I dominate it
algo te podría decir pues lo Domino
because it comes out of the four hairs that
porque me sale de los cuatro pelos que
I have left in my head
me quedaron en la cabeza
another thing is that you tell me that it has made a
otra cosa es que me digas que ha tenido
difference I believe if I am not mistaken that
diferencia creo si no me equivoco que
the data of the revit has been done and has been
los datos del revit han hecho y se han
put on the page
puesto en la página
I simply learn and smoke because
yo simplemente aprendo y fumo porque
simply the way of answering you can
simplemente la forma de responder se le
see that he is lying and that he knows what they
nota que está mintiendo y que sabe de lo
are talking about it is obvious
que le están hablando se le nota
dodging the subject and doing
esquivando el tema y haciendo la
gymnastics and a joke I don't know what you know
gimnasia y una broma yo no sé qué sabes
a round of applause for everyone and a like
un aplauso a todo el mundo y un like
everyone who is here an
todo el mundo que esté aquí un like
immediate like for nauter's The only
inmediato al de nauter El único canal de
gossip channel that is not my own that
salseo que no es el mío propio que no le
is not sucking Greg's balls and is
está comiendo los huevos al Greg y está
giving me publicity even though we do not
dándome difusión a pesar de que no nos
talk to each other but that's what there is the others are
hablamos pero es lo que hay los otros
some scared cowards sellouts you guys
unos achantados acojonados vendidos que
are sellouts This should not be
sois unos vendidos Es que esto no hay
kept quiet or for example made
que callarlo o por ejemplo hacerlo
funny you know it today eh they always do things
cachón sabela hoy eh siempre hacen cosas
and completely ignore the subject Why
y pasa del tema olímpicamente Por qué
Because they know what
Porque sabe lo que se está refiriendo
that super chat that they sent them is referring to or
ese súper chat que le han mandado o bien
not that is called no And you will say no it's that it
no que se llama no Y tú dirás no es que
is very acidic it exposes his dirty laundry
es muy ácido le saca los trapos sucios
okay But and Turbo plan with these
vale Pero y Turbo plan con estos
nominees have come out well from the people
nominados han salido pues de la gente
who have voted on reddit no and it is
que ha votado en el reddit no y se
supposed Well that the good ones in principle
supone Pues que los bueno en principio
were going to be 8 but in the end well there have been
iban a ser 8 pero al final pues han sido
10 the turbo plan the turbo plan Turbo
10 el turbo plan el turbo plan Turbo
plan they have released it I understand let's see
plan lo han sacado Yo entiendo a ver
but it was also in auto
pero es que también estaba en auto
named  I mean, about Turbo plan, I
denominado o sea lo de Turbo plan yo
understand that it's because of the
entiendo que es por el por el contenido
live content, no, it's true that
en directo no que sí que es verdad que a
I would have liked to have
turbopplan me hubiera gustado haberlo
nominated turbopplan too, to see how he would have
nominado también a ver cómo se hubiera
behaved, it wouldn't be the first time he
comportado no sería la primera vez que
had a plan, defend grefg and the group, he's already
tuvo plan defienda grefg y el grupito lo
done it, it seems curious to me that he
ha hecho ya a mí se me hace curioso que
had a plan, he specifically started
tuvo plan precisamente se haya puesto a
doing live shows, in the last month we
hacer directos en el último mes
were like among the top six seven
estábamos como entre los seis siete
but in the end. Well, now you'll
primeros pero al final Bueno ahora lo
see, in the end, grefa has done a bit of
veréis al final grefa ha hecho un poco
what she wanted. I do
lo que le ha salido del huevo izquierdo
n't know what happened, I was
no no sé qué ha pasado yo me he quedado
even surprised, even worse and more
hasta sorprendido incluso Peor y más
obvious since she was in sixth
evidente puesto que estaba en sexta
position, don't [ __ ] with me. I'm sad, no,
posición no me joda Estoy triste no
because the slams have come out and well,
porque han salido los slam y pues bueno
no, we are not nominated, there was
pues no no estamos nominados ha habido
a bit of a scam, thank goodness
ahí pues un poquito de tongo menos mal
my son, thank goodness my son, Turbo plan
hijo mío menos mal hijo mío Turbo plan
was in auto, of course. I understand that the
estaba en auto claro Yo entiendo que el
reason for kicking out Turbo plana, just
motivo de echar a Turbo plana al igual
like anoter, no. I mean, they were in Turbo plan
que anoter no O sea estaba en Turbo plan
inautter together. I mean, I think they were
inautter juntos O sea creo que estaban
fifth and sixth or something like that, but I
quinto y sexto o algo así pero yo
understood that it was because of the issue  of the
entendí que era por el tema de los
strings no because even though we
strings no porque a pesar de que
were sixth I believe in the voting and
estábamos sextos creo en la votación y
10 came out Well we haven't been
han salido 10 Pues no hemos salido
nominated Oh he doesn't do live eh one if he
nominados Ay no hace directo eh uno si
does and two this with Jordi Wild didn't
los hace y dos esto con Jordi Wild no
matter right it could be that they are not
importó verdad puede ser que no estén
enlightened I
iluminados
said that okay for the live shows but
eso lo dije vale por los directos pero
Jordi No no it's that he's more Jordi
Jordi No no es que es más Jordi también
was also nominated in news coverage I don't
estaba nominado en cobertura informativa
know if before but Probably yes at
no sé si antes pero Probablemente sí en
the top of naucher and turboplan not in the
lo alto de naucher y turboplan no en
middle in between imagine The seventh
medio entre medio imagínate El séptimo
eighth Jordi wiley project has done what his
octavo Jordi wiley project ha hecho lo
codons have come out with his
que le ha salido los codones con su
event of course I have done the
evento claro yo yo he hecho el directo
25 hour live show the live show of episode 100
de 25 horas el directo del episodio 100
Maybe I do two three live shows a year
A lo mejor hago dos tres directos al año
25 hours Do it yourself for me it would be a
25 horas Hazlo tú para mí sería un
spectacular scandal I
escándalo espectacular
shouldn't be there but Greg arrived and
no debería estar pero llego de Greg e
did magic there were some statements from
hizo magia había unas declaraciones de
Jordan and I think that effectively he will be there
Jordan y yo creo que efectivamente va a
if he is here first
estar si es que está aquí el primero
but that he does not comply with the Standard hey but it's that he goes
pero que no cumple con la Norma oye pero
first come on when will I
es que va primero venga va cuándo te
pay for your flight curiously just today they have
pago el vuelo curiosamente justo hoy han
returned he talks about him he said  what Gregor says
vuelto habla de él dijo lo que dice
now
ahora
[Laughs] he knows
[Risas]
very well he's a liar man he knows
sabe de sobra es un mentiroso tío sabe
very well that Jordi doesn't stream and he goes
de sobra que Jordi no hace Stream y coge
and when they tell him Well but you can't
y cuando le dicen Bueno pero a Jordi no
put Jordi no you don't stream he says
lo puedes meter no no haces Stream dice
no no but Jordi dad Jordi does a lot of live
no no pero Jordi papá Jordi hace muchos
streams he does a lot of live streams to [ __ ] off
directos hace mucho directo a tomar por
and I say that let's see because I don't want you to
culo y digo que ya a ver que no quiero
misunderstand me So it
que me que me malinterpretéis O sea que
's his event or rather imagine that the
es su evento o sea imaginaros que el
event is mine and I do a
evento es mío y yo hago un evento de
tennis event Well I give the gold cup not to the one who
tenis Pues yo le doy la copa de oro no
wins the most with the racket to the one I feel like it to the one who
al que no al que gane más con la raqueta
drops their
al que me dé la gana al que se bajen los
pants and falls in the middle of the field
pantalones y se cae en medio del campo
Hey but it's me more so much already but
Oye pero es que yo más tanto ya pero es
the rules say that whoever
que las normas dicen que en que cague el
defecates wins I don't know say it What do you do
que cague gana yo que sé dilo Qué haces
whatever the hell you want but don't say
lo que te sale de la [__] pero no digas
that about the community so that people don't
que de la comunidad que la gente no se
take it as something official so that everyone
lo tome como algo oficial que todos los
else doesn't promote you as if it were
demás no te promocionen como si fuera
something I told you because this detail
algo que te digo porque este detalle sí
should matter And be exclusive
que debería importar Y ser excluyente
because he's bald  baldness or the
porque está calvo calvofobia o los
community awards they call it
premios de la comunidad lo llaman a
all the nominees are these that you see
todos los nominados son estos que veis
on screen at least they are felicity or
en pantalla al menos están felicity o
sur representing a little but
sur un poco representando pero no
we are nowhere this is
estamos por ningún lado esto es
incredible not because representing many
increíble no porque representando muchas
of the people who have entered that in the
de las personas que han entrado que al
end have been 10 not like the stutterer
final han sido 10 no como el tartaja
Memories of a fish even nux Bot who has
Memorias de pez incluso a nux Bot que ha
entered with 26 votes and us with more
entrado con 26 votos y nosotros con más
than 170 votes is that to see I
de 170 votos es que por a ver yo
understand that because of the issue of the live shows something else
entiendo que por el tema de los directos
Javi I'm sure you will end up
otra cosa Javi seguro que tú acabarás
Knowing the truth you are very observant
Sabiendo la verdad eres muy observador
No I have already said it at the Airlines there is going to be
No yo ya lo he dicho en los Airlines va
movement there will be people who have
a haber movida va a haber gente que haya
fought there and her and come here and
peleado allí y ella y vengan para acá y
we find out there is going to be some problem
nos enteremos va a haber algún problema
with the tickets through Ticketmaster a thousand
con las entradas por Ticketmaster mil
things wait for the date that the eslam there
cosas esperaros a la fecha que los eslam
is movement remember and the worst thing is that it is going to
hay movidas acordaros y lo peor que me
catch me with my nose recently operated and
va a [__] con la nariz recién operada y
maybe I cannot work No
a lo mejor no puedo trabajar No a lo
maybe maybe I don't know maybe well
mejor quizás yo que sé a lo mejor pues
for some reason well I do not fall into
Por cierta razón pues no entro dentro de
the category or they have not considered me because  whether it
la categoría o no me han considerado por
really I mean, well
lo que sea que realmente O sea pues
man yes it makes me feel sorry but I feel more
hombre sí que me da pena pero me da más
sorry for the people who went to vote
pena por la gente no que ha ido a votar
there with all the enthusiasm and in the end of course
ahí con toda la ilusión y al final claro
it's like a little bit a little bit of a scam no I
es como un poquito un poquito estafa no
mean I can understand Obviously
O sea puedo llegar a entender Obviamente
in the end he does whatever the hell he wants
que al final pues haga lo que le dé la
not because they are his prizes but
gana no porque son sus premios pero
[ __ ] why do you do the voting
[__] porque haces lo de las votaciones
when later you go to collect the votes
cuando luego vas a [__] las votaciones
and you're going to do what you want no
y vas a hacer lo que te da la gana no
how Turbo loves the word scam
cómo le encanta la palabra estafa a
a little bit of a scam a little bit like
Turbo un poquito estafa un pelín como
when you throw salt and Gregorio listen to me
cuando echas sal y Gregorio hazme caso
don't try to separate yourself from any kind
no te intente desmarcar de ningún tipo
of equation when in the
de ecuación cuando en la categoría de
songs category you did what you wanted
canciones ha hecho lo que has querido
how you wanted
cómo has querido
songs already Casio the total disaster has
canciones ya Casio el desastre total ha
been already Look listen to me
sido ya Mira escúchame la categoría
I put the whole category by hand for the
entera la pongo yo a mano de las
songs since we're talking about
canciones ya es que estamos hablando de
tens of tens of thousands of votes eh
decenas de decenas de miles de votos eh
for the songs it has already been an
de las canciones ha sido ya una cosa
exaggerated thing eh first place was at home
exagerada eh primer puesto estaba a casa
Pete from Sprint then there was Juan
[__] de Sprint luego estaba Juan
Guarnizo with Ratio then he was alone
guarnizo con ratio después estaba solo
from Robleis again from Rodel and Barca
de robleis otra vez de rodezel y Barca
sea of doubts from Mariana  and then my
mar de dudas del Mariana y luego mi
parody song Stay funda version of
canción parodia Quédate versión funda de
Auron and To my surprise This is the
auron y Para mi sorpresa Esta es la
list of the nominees that have been
lista de los nominados que se han
published and they do not appear anywhere
publicado y no aparecen en ningún lado
my parody song Stay funa version
mi canción parodia Quédate versión funa
nor to home Pete by Sprint nor
ni tampoco a casa [__] de Sprint ni
ratio by Juan guarnizo nor the
tampoco ratio de Juan guarnizo ni la
song by zorman and we were among the
canción de zorman y estábamos entre los
top 10 This has generated a
10 primeros Esto me ha generado una
tremendous disappointment in me
tremenda desilusión
The proud one, the happy one with the decision he has
El orgulloso el contento con la decisión
made Although he represents String
que ha tomado Aunque representa String
Although he represents Juan, I think there have to
Aunque represente a Juan creo que tiene
be streamers, artists who make
que estar streamers artistas que haga
music and who have released their songs, no,
música y que hayan sacado sus temas no
of course we have to congratulate Gregorio, he
desde luego hay que felicitar a Gregorio
has achieved something quite complicated,
ha conseguido algo bastante complicado
that everyone thinks the same on two
que todo el mundo piense igual en dos
points unanimously that the
puntos unánime que el sistema de
voting system has been complete
votaciones ha sido una completa
crap and that what he has done with the
porquería y que lo que ha hecho con la
musical section makes no [ __ ] sense
sección musical no tiene [__] sentido
there is also something else that Greg has achieved,
hay otra cosa también que ha conseguido
that Juan guarnizo
de Greg que Juan guarnizo de repente
is suddenly based the other day with
esté basadísimo el otro día con el
chocas I felt the direct attack when he
chocas yo sentí el ataque directo cuando
says that who wins the
dice que quién gana las categoría
streamer of the year category is the one with the most young children, so that is why
streamer del año el que más niños
Juan guarnizo was just there El Mariana  and Sprint
estar Juan guarnizo El Mariana y Sprint
I swear that was when I said
yo te lo juro que ahí fue cuando ya dije
okay because it doesn't make sense to mess with
ok porque no tiene sentido meterse con
my people I mean it doesn't make sense to mess
mi gente O sea no tiene sentido meterse
with my audience I don't mess with the
con mi audiencia Yo no me meto con la
shock audience Come to Choco
audiencia del shock Ven al chocas a
daily the hours they want to see it
diario las horas que quieren verlo a
daily and they will have their reasons and let's
diario y sus motivos tendrán y
remember one thing friends the audience
recordemos una cosa amigos la audiencia
whether they are 12 years old or 30 is still an
ya sea de 12 años o de 30 sigue siendo
audience and they deserve respect not so many
audiencia y merecen un respeto no tantos
years
años
you want that person with hot blood
quieres esa persona con sangre caliente
that you feel like you're pissing in your
que sientes que te estás meando en la
face you learn directly you say four
cara aprendes directo dices cuatro
barbarities that may be well
barbaridades que pueden estar bien
said and you may be right and then the
dichas y puedes tener razón y luego la
[ __ ] thing is heated
[__] que calentada
[ __ ] some awards that are
[__] unos premios que son unas
songs of course are songs for the
canciones claro son canciones para la
community It's that he missed putting Bad
comunidad Es que le ha faltado poner Bad
Bunny neverita it's not that of course
Bunny neverita no es que claro
Bad Bunny really logical that as
Bad Bunny de verdad lógico que como dice
Spring says he wants to piss in your face I don't care I
Spring se quiera mear en tu cara
was live today saying like
estuve en directo diciendo hoy como
aleta and that's it we were like 6
aleta y ya está no estuvimos como 6
hours with a tortilla that night doing that
horas con tortita esa noche haciendo eso
dude we're talking about that he
boludo estamos hablando de que
literally took an award out of his
literalmente le ha quitado un premio de
hands let's be honest if ratio and
las manos seamos honestos si ratio y a
home Pete would have reached the
casa [__] hubieran llegado a la
category  that most likely they would have done it
categoría que muy probablemente lo
would have won at home
Hubieran hecho hubiera ganado a casa
Pete because it was quite a bit more viral
[__] porque fue bastante más viral a
even though radio was very viral at home
pesar de que radio fue muy viral a casa
Pete was a little bit more viral and it was the
[__] fue un poco más viral y fue la
first of these songs it was shorter
primera de estas canciones era más corta
people have more memorized at home Pete
la gente tiene más memorizada casa [__]
So I'm not saying it because I was
Entonces yo no lo digo porque yo me
going to win the award with ratio no
fuera a ganar el premio con ratio no
definitely not but I think that Sprint
definitivamente no pero creo que Sprint
has to at least value the time that
tiene por lo menos valorar el tiempo que
you guys were voting on that reddit
estuvieron ustedes votando en ese reddit
with the nomination that is nominated that was
con la nominación que está nominado que
the one that was nominated and that's it I mean
era el que estaba nominado y punto O sea
that was the one that was nominated and that's it So there is
que era el que estaba nominado y punto
no more to which it should
Así que no hay más al cual debía de
happen and as the rules were stipulated it
pasar y tal cual estaban estipuladas las
seemed right to me thinking about it
reglas me parecía lo correcto pensándole
carefully a large part of the blame for all this
bien gran parte de culpa de toda esta
controversy is on us all for giving
polémica la tenemos todos por darles
importance to these awards therefore
importancia a estos premios por lo tanto
as I would say and I Juan always wins
como diría y yo Juan de siempre gana
This is already becoming a [ __ ]
Esto se está convirtiendo ya en una [__]
madness our fault our fault let's not
locura culpa Nuestra culpa nuestra no
blame the public our fault that we
culpemos al público culpa nuestra que
all have in the end our ego we all
todos tenemos al final nuestro ego todos
have our things We all want to
tenemos nuestra cosas Todos queremos
win the awards that recognize us we have to be
ganar los premios que nos lo reconozcan
honest friends it is being
hay que ser sinceros amigos se está
noticed it is being noticed that the
notando se está notando que los premios
gref awards matter they are like  the oscars, to
de gref importan son como los oscars a
me, honestly, there are no other
mí de verdad que tampoco hay otros
big awards, I mean, in the
grandes premios o sea lo que es en la
Spanish-speaking community they only do it
comunidad hispanohablante solo lo hacen
coscu and it only does it for Argentina, it's being
coscu y solo lo hace para argentina se
noticed, everyone is pushing a
está notando cada uno está apretando un
little bit for the award.
poquito para para el premio ya por
Finally, the YouTube platform seems to
último la plataforma de YouTube parece
have little importance and this is
que tiene poca importancia y aquí es
where DJ posh comes into the scene, but it's
donde aparece en escena Dj pija pero es
true that he's right,
verdad que tiene razón
okay. But well, he's not there, although he
vale Pero bueno no está aunque tampoco
's not there much either since he does
está mucho puesto que su presencia sí
have a presence and he goes and spoke specifically about the
que tiene y va y hablaba en específico
award for streamer of the year, but I don't
al premio al streamer del año pero no
agree with what a lot of people
estoy de acuerdo con lo que mucha gente
say that because he's on YouTube he's
dice que por estar en YouTube se le
marginalized. It's not true that Mario has a
margina No es cierto di Mario tiene
nomination for event of the year and he's made people angry,
nominación evento del año y ha enfado
so people
del año entonces la gente cuando quiere
remember him when they want, I mean, for the community
se acuerda de él o sea para la comunidad
they've said, he's got the year, I don't care,
han dicho Oye tiene el año no me la pela
angry, yes, it makes me laugh a lot,
enfadado sí me hace mucha risa
the community
la comunidad
that is on YouTube, people, of course, he was the
que es en YouTube la gente claro era el
first on reddit, you know what I want to
primero en reddit sabes lo que te quiero
tell you and you. You also remember
decir y tú Tú también estás acordado de
Jordi, dude, you remember what you
Jordi güey tú te acuerdas de lo que
want, but speaking of YouTube that isn't there,
quieres pero hablando de YouTube que no
something that I find totally
está algo que me parece totalmente
regrettable.  God Vegeta Vegeta would not
lamentable el Dios vegetita Vegeta no
go if Vegeta had been nominated he is
iría si Vegeta hubiera estado nominado
not going and he is going to take away value from the
no va y va a ir quitándole valor a los
awards No no it is the truth if it is
premios No no es que es la verdad si es
the problem here of course he
que el problema aquí que claro que se
is taking something This kid as
está tomando una cosa Este chaval como
if it were official but the
si fuera lo oficial pero es que con el
same thing happens with the rewin he is very handsome
rewin pasa lo mismo que está muy guapo
edited it is very well put together and everything you
editado está muy bien montado y todo lo
want but they have taken it as something
que queráis pero lo han tomado como algo
official and they are doing the Canelo
oficial y están haciendo el Canelo
because everyone else is collaborating with these things for
porque es que a estas cosas están
free gref would never put
gratuitamente gref nunca metería a
Vegeta in with that no no but apart from that
Vegeta con eso no no pero es que aparte
Vegeta would not go I'm telling you 177 is not
Vegeta no iría ya te lo digo yo 177 no
Willy is not it is not simply a
está Willy no esta No es simplemente
question don't hate me questioned for
pregunta no me odies cuestionado por
it and for Willy he received The donation
ello y por Willy le llegó La donación
that you have heard well pay attention to
que habéis escuchado pues atención a
how he ignores them and takes it with cognac I
como los ningunea y se lo toma a coñac
am going to put it on the page now in
lo voy a meter yo ahora en la página de
fact I am going to start programming the
hecho me voy a poner a programar la
page
página
you know what happens dear that
sabes lo que pasa querido que
surely they do not want to have anything to
seguramente ellos no quieren tener nada
do with something in which so much
que ver en algo en lo que tanto
involved and their audience knows it
implicado y su audiencia lo sabe Por
Therefore they were not going to turn out to vote for him
ende no se iba a volcar para votarlo lo
what  I don't know and I know that
que desconozco y conozco yo se ha colado
Karmaland 5 has snuck in there But I hope they win so
ahí Karmaland 5 Pero ojalá ganen para
that they leave you stranded even by
que te dejen tirado hasta por
video call If Karmaland wins,
videollamada si gana Karmaland lo
El Rubius will pick it up No, El Rubius did
recogerá El Rubius no El Rubius a los
n't go to Slash Something also happened and some
Slash no fue pasó algo también y algún
nonsense or something like that Willy wouldn't
rollo o algo por el estilo Willy tampoco
go either, man of course he wouldn't go obviously but not
iría hombre claro no iría evidentemente
even to the call as
pero ni a la llamada como ha dicho
nauter said but Karmaland won't win I think
nauter pero no gana Karmaland yo creo
that Squid Games wins more than
que ganan los juegos del calamar más que
anything because of the revolution that was we all
nada por la revolución que fue todos
think that gossip is not something
pensamos que el salseo no es algo
positive we have that anger that
positivo le tenemos ese esa rabia ese
disgust but then we consume it
asco pero luego lo consumimos
how we like
cómo nos gusta
no comments
sin comentarios
[Music]
[Música]